

CONTACT



neelujun07@gmail.com



+91-8744966754



559/A Flat #1, FF, Dayanand Colony, Gurugram, HR

SKILLS

- Technical Support and Assistance
- Microsoft Windows and Office
- Customer Satisfaction and Retention
- Policy and Procedure Adherence
- Problem Solving and Data Analysis
- Call Volume and Quality Metrics
- Complex Product Knowledge
- Active Listening Skills
- **Empathetic and Courteous**

LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Hindi Native

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Over 9 years of experience in Customer Service. Hardworking professional with experience in business operations, technical support and customer service. Highly organized and self-motivated with excellent communication and interpersonal skills. Demonstrated ability to prioritize tasks and meet deadlines

EXPERIENCE

March 2023 - Present

Customer Relationship Executive

AG Consultancy, Gurugram, Haryana

October 2019 – October 2022

Process Developer

Genpact, Gurugram, Haryana

February 2016 – December 2016

Customer Service Manager

NR Ventures Pvt. Ltd, Gurugram, Haryana

April 2012 - July 2015

Sr. Customer Service Executive

IndiaBulls Technology Solutions Ltd, Gurugram, Haryana

January 2011 – February 2012

Technical Support Officer

Convergys India Service Pvt. Ltd, Gurugram, Haryana

EDUCATION

August 2006 – June 2010

Bachelors of Technology in Information Technology

BBDNITM, Lucknow, UP

CERTIFICATION

Java, C++, Asp.net Customer service strategy training